http://www.akroncantonfoodbank.org/privacy

Community Harvest
Resources & ReportsNeed Food?
Contact UsStaff Directory
Get InvolvedJoin our Partner NetworkNew Partner Application Process
Privacy Policy
The Akron-Canton Regional Foodbank shares your concerns about privacy on the Internet. In order to better protect your privacy, the Akron-Canton Regional Foodbank has provided this notice explaining its online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used on the Site. Furthermore, this Privacy Policy, being part of the Terms, works in conjunction with the Terms and Conditions of Use, but does not modify or supercede it.
We will not sell, trade or share your personal information with anyone else, and we will not send mailings on behalf of other organizations. We will only share personal information if you give us specific permission to do so. If you wish to be removed from our mailing list, please contact us at 330.535.6900 or info@acrfb.org.
The Akron-Canton Regional Foodbank's Collection and Use of Your Information
In the course of using the Site, the Akron-Canton Regional Foodbank may ask you for your name, e-mail address, postal address, telephone number, fax number as well as other relevant information. The Akron-Canton Regional Foodbank also may collect certain non-personally identifiable information when you visit many of our web pages such as the type of browser you are using, the type of operating system you are using, the domain name of your Internet service provider, aggregate data about the number of visits to the Site and/or aggregate data about the pages visited.
How The Akron-Canton Regional Foodbank Uses the Information
The Akron-Canton Regional Foodbank uses the non-personally identifiable information ("Aggregate Data") to improve the design and content of the Site and to enable the Akron-Canton Regional Foodbank to personalize your Internet experience. The Akron-Canton Regional Foodbank may use the Aggregate Data to analyze Site usage as well as create services and/or products to fit your needs. Also, the Akron-Canton Regional Foodbank shares this Aggregate Data with the Akron-Canton Regional Foodbank's related entities, advertisers, partners and/or other third party vendors. The Akron-Canton Regional Foodbank shall own such Aggregate Data and maintain copies of such as part of its records.
Except as otherwise indicated, the Akron-Canton Regional Foodbank uses the personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") you provide about yourself: (a) to respond to any of your inquiries or questions about our services; (b) for internal marketing purposes and as part of the Akron-Canton Regional Foodbank's donor database; (c) to provide you additional and updated information, materials and other advertisements regarding the Akron-Canton Regional Foodbank services; (d) to offer you other materials and/or information that the Akron-Canton Regional Foodbank believes may be of interest to you; (e) to cooperate with government officials or parties in litigation under process of law, or as otherwise required by law; (f) to protect the security or integrity of the Site; (g) to protect against a threat of safety or destruction of property; and/or (h) to protect against legal liability. In all cases, however, the Akron-Canton Regional Foodbank agents, employees and contractors who have access to Personal Information are required to protect this information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy.
Furthermore, the Akron-Canton Regional Foodbank encourages all its business Partners to adopt and adhere to standards of protection consistent with this Privacy Policy. The Akron-Canton Regional Foodbank will not use the Personal Information, except as set forth herein, without your permission; provided, however, the Akron-Canton Regional Foodbank shall own all such Personal Information and maintain copies of such as part of its records. If you do not wish to receive any such information or to allow the Akron-Canton Regional Foodbank the right to use your personally identifiable information as described, please contact the Akron-Canton Regional Foodbank in the manner identified in the "Opt-Out" section below. The Aggregate Data and Personal Information may be transferred, distributed or sold as part of the Akron-Canton Regional Foodbank or its assets.
Opt Out
You may choose not to receive such information and/or to allow the Akron-Canton Regional Foodbank to use your information in the manner described above by simply notifying the Akron-Canton Regional Foodbank directly at www.akroncantonfoodbank.org or at 330-535-6900. Upon receipt and processing of an "opt out" request, the Akron-Canton Regional Foodbank will, within its commercially reasonable amount of time, remove your information from any future marketing communications.
Security; No Liability
The Akron-Canton Regional Foodbank has implemented security measures to help protect against the risk of loss, misuse and alteration of any information under the Akron-Canton Regional Foodbank's control. The Akron-Canton Regional Foodbank protects your online order information by using Secure Sockets Layer ("SSL") technology. SSL encrypts your order information to avoid the decoding of that information by anyone other than the Akron-Canton Regional Foodbank. Nevertheless, such security measures may not prevent all loss, misuse or alteration of information on the Site, and the Akron-Canton Regional Foodbank is not responsible for any damages or liabilities relating to any such security failures. You understand that data and communications, including e-mail and other electronic communications, may be accessed by unauthorized third parties when communicated over the Internet. Furthermore, the Site contains links to other web sites. The Akron-Canton Regional Foodbank is not responsible for nor can the Akron-Canton Regional Foodbank ensure the privacy practices or content of such other sites.
IP Addresses and Cookies
Like other web sites, the Akron-Canton Regional Foodbank uses your IP address to help diagnose problems with the Akron-Canton Regional Foodbank's servers, to administer the Site and for security purposes.
"Cookies" are pieces of data sent from a Web server to a Web browser that enable a Web server to identify users that visit a site hosted by that server. The Akron-Canton Regional Foodbank may use Cookies in order to identify you to our site so that the Akron-Canton Regional Foodbank can provide more customized information and services to you. In addition, our site may contain advertisements that may contain Cookies. In general, if you choose, you can disable the use of Cookies by reviewing your browser's preferences and options.
Modification of Privacy Policy
The Akron-Canton Regional Foodbank may change this Privacy Policy at any time, consistent with the terms set forth in the Terms and Conditions of Use, by posting the changed or amended Privacy Policy on the Site. Your continued viewing of or use of this Site following the posting of any changes to this Privacy Policy will signify your assent to any such changes or amendments.
How to Contact the Akron-Canton Regional Foodbank for Any Reason
You may contact the Akron-Canton Regional Foodbank with questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy, updating any personally identifiable information or anything else related to the Akron-Canton Regional Foodbank and/or this Site at www.akroncantonfoodbank.org or at 330-535-6900.
TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF USE
1. INTRODUCTION.
Welcome to the web site ("Site") for the Akron-Canton Regional Foodbank ("the Akron-Canton Regional Foodbank").
2. ACCESS TO THE SITE.
BY ACCESSING, BROWSING AND/OR USING THE SITE, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOU HAVE READ, UNDERSTOOD AND AGREED TO BE BOUND BY THESE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF USE ("TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF USE"), INCLUDING THE PRIVACY POLICY ("PRIVACY POLICY") [LINK], (COLLECTIVELY, THE "TERMS") AND TO COMPLY WITH ALL APPLICABLE U.S. LAWS AND REGULATIONS. If you do not or cannot agree to the Terms, do not use the Site or any of the services offered through the Site. The Akron-Canton Regional Foodbank reserves the right, in its sole discretion, to update, revise, supplement and to otherwise modify these Terms, and to impose new or additional terms and conditions on your use of the Site from time to time. Such updates, revisions, supplements, modifications and additional rules, polices, terms and conditions (collectively referred to in these Terms as "Additional Terms") will be effective immediately and incorporated into these Terms upon notice thereof, which may be given by any reasonable means including by posting to the Site. Your continued viewing or use of the Site following such notice will be deemed to conclusively indicate your acceptance of any and all such Additional Terms.
3. ACCEPTABLE USE OF THE SITE.
In order to use the Site, you must obtain access to the Internet and pay any and all service fees associated with such access.
(a) Individual Use. You agree that you are only authorized to visit, view and to retain a single copy of pages of the Site for your own internal use and not for any commercially-related purposes or in a manner that in any way suggests a connection, affiliation or any type of relationship between the Akron-Canton Regional Foodbank and you or an entity related to you. You also agree that you will not duplicate, download, publish, modify or otherwise distribute any material on the Site for any purpose other than for your own internal use unless otherwise specifically authorized by the Akron-Canton Regional Foodbank in writing. The Akron-Canton Regional Foodbank posts legal notices and various credits on pages of the Site, which may not be removed even in your permitted copies. Do not remove these notices or credits, or any additional information contained along with the notices and credits.
(b) Deep Links; Linking. You agree not to "deep-link" to the Site, meaning that you will not create, post, display, publish or distribute any link to any page other than the front (home) page of the Site for any purpose, unless specifically authorized by the Akron-Canton Regional Foodbank in writing to do so. If you do want to link to the Site in any manner, please contact the Akron-Canton Regional Foodbank Webmaster at www.akroncantonfoodbank.org to seek approval.
(c) Framing. You agree not to create any frames at any other web sites pertaining to or using any of the content located at the Site for any purpose, unless specifically authorized by the Akron-Canton Regional Foodbank in writing to do so.
(d) Security, Cracking and Hacking. You are prohibited from violating or attempting to violate the security of the Site. Accordingly, you agree not to: (i) access data or materials not intended for you; (ii) log into a server or account which you are not authorized to access; (iii) attempt to probe, scan or test the vulnerability of a system or network or to breach security or authentication measures without proper authorization; or (iv) attempt to interfere with service to any user, host or network, including without limitation, by means of submitting a virus to the Site, overloading, "flooding", "mailbombing" or "crashing" the Site. Violations of system or network security may result in civil or criminal liability. The Akron-Canton Regional Foodbank reserves the right to investigate occurrences which may involve such violations and may involve, and cooperate with, law enforcement authorities in prosecuting users who have participated in such violations. You understand that data and communications, including e-mail and other electronic communications, may be accessed by unauthorized third parties when communicated over the Internet.
(e) You Are Responsible For All of Your Activities and All of The Content You Post or Submit. You represent and warrant that any information and/or material you post or provide to the Akron-Canton Regional Foodbank by means of the Site, including, without limitation, as part of any registration or subscription or to gain access to or use any services offered on the Site ("Submissions"), is truthful, accurate, not misleading, not confidential property of others, not in violation of any other third party's rights and offered in good faith. You agree NOT to use the Site for or in connection with any of the following activities: (i) transmitting or relaying spam, spoofing or otherwise impersonating any person or entity, or falsely stating or otherwise misrepresenting your identity or affiliation in any way; (ii) using the Site for any fraudulent or illegal purpose; (iii) e-mailing, uploading, or otherwise transmitting or using the Site in furtherance of the use, distribution or transmission of any unlawful, harassing, defamatory, tortious, libelous, sexually explicit, obscene, hateful, racially, ethnically or otherwise objectionable material of any kind; and (iv) transmitting material that contains viruses, Trojan horses, worms, time bombs, cancelbots or other computer programming routines or engines that are intended to damage, destroy, disrupt or otherwise impair a computer's functionality or the operation of the Site.
(f) Do Not Violate Third Party Intellectual Property Rights. Without limiting the foregoing, you may not, and by using the Site you agree not to, use the Site to: (i) transmit or post any Submissions that are copyrighted, unless you are the copyright owner or have obtained the permission of the copyright owner to transmit it; (ii) transmit or post any Submissions that reveal trade secrets, unless you own them or have the permission of the owner to so transmit them; or (iii) transmit or post any Submissions that infringe on any Intellectual Property Rights (as defined below) of others or violates the privacy or rights of publicity of others. Furthermore, unless otherwise expressly provided, you acknowledge and agree that: (a) all Submissions will become property of the Akron-Canton Regional Foodbank; (b) the Akron-Canton Regional Foodbank has the right to publish the Submissions for any type of use including for promotional and advertising purposes, in accordance with the terms set forth in the Privacy Policy, without compensation to you of any kind; (c) any Submissions that you submit to any part of the Site are non-confidential for all purposes; and (d) that if you make any such Submission, you automatically grant, represent and warrant that the owner of such content has expressly granted the Akron-Canton Regional Foodbank a royalty-free, perpetual, irrevocable, world-wide exclusive license to use the Submissions in any manner, media or form now known or hereafter developed. The Akron-Canton Regional Foodbank shall have the right to sublicense its rights. The term "Intellectual Property Rights" means collectively, rights under patent, trademark, copyright and trade secret laws, and any other intellectual property or proprietary rights recognized in any country or jurisdiction worldwide including, without limitation, moral rights and similar rights.
(g) Ownership. The Akron-Canton Regional Foodbank puts a lot of content on the Site for you to examine from time to time including, without limitation, text, graphics, photographs, pictures, drawings, animation, audio, video, literature and any other material distributed by the Akron-Canton Regional Foodbank on, through or in connection with the Site. Moreover, the Akron-Canton Regional Foodbank attempts to display the content in a way that will be easily accessible and useful for you, the user. All content and materials on the Site including, without limitation, text, graphics, logos, button icons, images, audio clips and software included in the Site and any services offered on the Site, are the property of the Akron-Canton Regional Foodbank, its sponsors or business affiliates, and/or their respective licensors, and are subject to U.S. and international Intellectual Property Rights laws. The compilation of all content on the Site is the exclusive property of the Akron-Canton Regional Foodbank and is protected by U.S. and international copyright laws. All software used on the Site is the property of the Akron-Canton Regional Foodbank or its licensors and is subject to U.S. and international copyright laws. Except to the minimum extent otherwise expressly permitted under copyright law, no copying or exploitation of material from the Site is permitted except expressly in accordance with these Terms or with the express written permission of the Akron-Canton Regional Foodbank and any other applicable copyright owner. You acknowledge that you do not acquire any ownership rights by virtue of downloading copyrighted material from the Site. All rights not expressly granted hereunder are expressly reserved to the Akron-Canton Regional Foodbank.
(h) Spidering. THE USE OF ANY TOOLS, PROGRAMS, ROBOTIC ALGORITHMS OR PRODUCTS TO AUTOMATICALLY DOWNLOAD OR "SPIDER" THE SITE OR ANY OF THE PAGES OF THE SITE INFRINGES ON THE AKRON-CANTON REGIONAL FOODBANK'S AND/OR ITS LICENSORS' INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY RIGHTS. DO NOT USE ANY SUCH TOOLS OR PRODUCTS ON OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SITE.
4. WARRANTY DISCLAIMER.
THE CONTENT, SERVICES, INFORMATION AND ACCESS TO THE SITE ARE PROVIDED "AS IS" AND WITHOUT WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, SATISFACTORY QUALITY AND NON-INFRINGEMENT. THE AKRON-CANTON REGIONAL FOODBANK DOES NOT WARRANT THAT ANY PART OF THE SITE WILL OPERATE UNINTERRUPTED OR ERROR-FREE, THAT DEFECTS WILL BE CORRECTED, OR THAT THE SITE OR THE SERVER THAT MAKES IT AVAILABLE ARE FREE OF VIRUSES OR OTHER HARMFUL COMPONENTS OR THAT TRANSMISSION TO OR FROM THE SITE AND ACCESS TO THE SITE WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED, CONTINUOUS OR ERROR-FREE. THE AKRON-CANTON REGIONAL FOODBANK DOES NOT WARRANT OR MAKE ANY REPRESENTATIONS REGARDING THE USE OR THE RESULTS OF THE USE OF THE SITE IN TERMS OF ITS QUALITY, CORRECTNESS, ACCURACY, RELIABILITY, OR OTHERWISE. YOU SHOULD THEREFORE VERIFY ANY INFORMATION OBTAINED FROM THE SITE BEFORE ACTING ON IT. EXCEPT AS OTHERWISE EXPRESSLY PROVIDED, THE AKRON-CANTON REGIONAL FOODBANK EXPRESSLY DISCLAIMS ANY RESPONSIBILITY FOR THE ACCURACY, CONTENT, AVAILABILITY OF INFORMATION, PRODUCTS, SERVICES OR MERCHANDISE FOUND ON THIRD PARTY SITES THAT LINK TO OR FROM THE SITE. THE AKRON-CANTON REGIONAL FOODBANK DISCLAIMS ANY RESPONSIBILITY FOR PRODUCT OR SERVICE ORDERING FUNCTIONS, ORDER FULFILLMENT OR COMPLIANCE OF PRODUCTS OR SERVICES WITH ANY MANUFACTURER'S WARRANTIES OR SPECIFICATIONS. THE AKRON-CANTON REGIONAL FOODBANK CANNOT BE HELD RESPONSIBLE FOR THE MATERIAL CONTAINED ON THIRD PARTY SITES AND/OR RELATED SERVICES NOR DOES THE AKRON-CANTON REGIONAL FOODBANK MAKE ANY REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES AS TO THE SECURITY OF ANY INFORMATION YOU MIGHT BE REQUESTED TO GIVE TO THIRD PARTY SITES.
5. LIMITATION OF LIABILITY.
YOUR USE OF THE SITE IS AT YOUR OWN RISK. TO THE FURTHEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW, UNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCES INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, THE AKRON-CANTON REGIONAL FOODBANK'S NEGLIGENCE, SHALL THE AKRON-CANTON REGIONAL FOODBANK BE LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGES INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, DIRECT, SPECIAL, INDIRECT, PUNITIVE, CONSEQUENTIAL, EXEMPLARY AND/OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES THAT RESULT FROM YOUR USE OR INABILITY TO USE THE SITE, ANY CONTENT AND/OR ANY RELATED SOFTWARE, EVEN IF THE AKRON-CANTON REGIONAL FOODBANK OR AN AUTHORIZED AKRON-CANTON REGIONAL FOODBANK REPRESENTATIVE HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. NOTWITHSTANDING ANYTHING ELSE CONTAINED IN THESE TERMS, IN THE EVENT THE TERMS OF THIS SECTION, OR ANY PART OF THIS SECTION, SHALL BE HELD INVALID OR UNENFORCEABLE BY A COURT OF COMPETENT JURISDICTION, IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AKRON-CANTON REGIONAL FOODBANK'S TOTAL LIABILITY TO YOU, OR ANYONE CLAIMING BY OR THROUGH YOU, FOR ANY DAMAGES, LOSSES, CLAIMS AND/OR CAUSES OF ACTION, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, TORT, NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE EXCEED ONE HUNDRED DOLLARS ($100).
6. INDEMNIFICATION.
You shall indemnify, defend and hold harmless the Akron-Canton Regional Foodbank and its sponsors, business affiliates, subsidiaries, affiliates, officers, directors, employees, attorneys and agents, from and against any and all damages, claims and actions brought by you or any third party resulting from your use of the Site in violation of these Terms or the infringement by you of any Intellectual Property Rights of any person or entity.
7. GOVERNING LAW AND ARBITRATION.
The laws of the State of Ohio (excluding any principles of conflicts of laws) govern your use of the Site, the services and these Terms. You agree that the parties shall settle any claim or dispute relating to these Terms by binding arbitration in Akron, Ohio under the Commercial Arbitration Rules of the American Arbitration Association. To the fullest extent permitted by applicable law, no arbitration under these Terms shall be joined to an arbitration involving any other party subject to these Terms, whether through class arbitration proceedings or otherwise. NOTWITHSTANDING THE DISPUTE RESOLUTION REQUIREMENTS SET FORTH ABOVE, FOR ANY INJUNCTIVE RELIEF RELATING TO YOUR ACCESS TO, OR USE OF, THE SITE INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, RELATED SERVICES, YOU AGREE AND HEREBY SUBMIT TO THE EXCLUSIVE JURISDICTION AND VENUE OF THE APPROPRIATE STATE OR FEDERAL COURTS LOCATED IN SUMMIT COUNTY, OHIO, U.S.A.
8. WAIVER AND SEVERABILITY.
Furthermore, no delay or omission by the Akron-Canton Regional Foodbank to exercise any right or any noncompliance on your part with respect to the Terms shall impair any such right or be construed to be a waiver by the Akron-Canton Regional Foodbank. If any provision of the Terms is found by a court of competent jurisdiction to be invalid or unenforceable in whole or in part, such provision shall, as to such jurisdiction, be ineffective to the extent of such invalidity or unenforceability without in any manner affecting the validity or enforceability thereof in any other jurisdiction or the remaining provisions hereof in any jurisdiction, provided, however, if such invalid or unenforceable provision may be modified so as to be valid and enforceable as a matter of law, such provision will be deemed to have been modified so as to be valid and enforceable to the maximum extent permitted by law.
9. CONTRACT ELECTRONICALLY.
You agree that the Terms, combined with your act of using the Site and/or the services offered on or through the Site have the same legal force and effect as a written contract with your written signature and satisfy any laws that require a writing or signature, including any applicable Statute of Frauds. You further agree that you shall not challenge the validity, enforceability or admissibility of the Terms on the grounds that it was electronically transmitted or authorized. In addition, you acknowledge that you have had the opportunity to print the Terms.
Privacy Policy • Staff Links • Board Portal
© All rights reserved.
